Guide to The Polytechnic Reporter RG.025
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
The Polytechnic Reporter
1914-2014
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.025
25
9 Linear Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
- Series I: Loose newspapers
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 February 11, 7541 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 February 18, 7545 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 February 26, 7549 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 5, 7553 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 12, 7557 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 19, 7561 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 26, 7565 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 2, 7569 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 9, 7573 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 23, 7577 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 30, 7581 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 May 7, 7585 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 May 14, 7589 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 May 21, 7593 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 June 12, 7601 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 September 24, 7605 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 1, 7609 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 8, 7613 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 15, 7617 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 22, 7621 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 29, 7625 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 5, 7629 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 12, 7633 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 19, 7637 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 25, 7641 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 December 3, 7645 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 December 10, 7649 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 December 17, 7653 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 January 7, 7657 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 January 14, 7661 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 January 21, 7665 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 4, 7669 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 11, 7673 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 18, 7677 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 25, 7681 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 4, 7685 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 11, 7689 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 18, 7693 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 25, 7697 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 1, 7701 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 15, 7705 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 22, 7709 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 29, 7713 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 6, 7717 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 13, 7721 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 20, 7725 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 27, 7729 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 September 30, 7733 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 7, 7737 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 14, 7741 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 21, 7745 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 28, 7753 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 November 11, 7757 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 November 18, 7761 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 2, 7765 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 9, 7769 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 16, 7773 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 23, 7777 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 January 6, 7781 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 January 13, 7785 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 February 3, 7789 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 February 10, 7793 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 February 25, 7798 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 2, 7802 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 9, 7806 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 16, 7810 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 23, 7814 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 April 13, 7818 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 April 20, 7822 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 April 27, 7826 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 May 4, 7830 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 May 11, 7834 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 May 18, 7838 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 September 28, 7842 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 5, 7846 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 13, 7850 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 19, 7854 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 26, 7858 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 2, 7862 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 9, 7866 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 16, 7870 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 23, 7874 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 December 7, 7880 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 December 14, 7884 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 December 21, 7888 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 January 4, 7892 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 January 11, 7896 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 1, 7900 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 8, 7904 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 15, 7908 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 22, 7914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 1, 7918 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 8, 7924 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 15, 7928 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 22, 7932 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 29, 7936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 April 5, 7940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 April 19, 7946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 April 26, 7950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 3, 7954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 10, 7958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 17, 7962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 24, 7966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 4, 7970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 11, 7974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 18, 7978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 25, 7982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 1, 7986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 8, 7990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 15, 7994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 22, 7998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 December 6, 8004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 December 23, 8008 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 January 10, 8015 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 January 31, 8019 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 7, 8023 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 14, 8029 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 21, 8033 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 28, 8037 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 7, 8041 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 14, 8045 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 21, 8049 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 28, 8053 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 April 11, 8057 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 2, 8063 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 9, 8069 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 16, 8073 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 23, 8077 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 October 10, 8081 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 October 17, 8085 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 October 24, 8089 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 7, 8095 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 14, 8099 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 21, 8103 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 29, 8107 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 December 6, 8111 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 December 13, 8115 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 December 20, 8119 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 10, 8125 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 17, 8129 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 24, 8133 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 31, 8137 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 7, 8141 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 14, 8145 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 21, 8149 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 28, 8153 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 7, 8157 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 14, 8161 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 21, 8165 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 28, 8169 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 April 4, 8173 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 April 11, 8181 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 April 18, 8187 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 2, 8193 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 9, 8199 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 16, 8205 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 23, 8209 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 3, 8213 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 10, 8217 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 17, 8221 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 31, 8226 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 November 7, 8229 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 November 26, 8235 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 December 5, 8241 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 December 12, 8245 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 December 19, 8249 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 January 9, 8253 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 January 30, 8257 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 6, 8263 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 13, 8267 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 20, 8271 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 27, 8275 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 5, 8279 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 12, 8283 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 19, 8287 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 26, 8291 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 April 16, 8297 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 April 23, 8301 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 April 30, 8305 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 7, 8309 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 14, 8313 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 21, 8319 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 28, 8323 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 1, 8329 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 8, 8333 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 15, 8337 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 22, 8341 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 29, 8349 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 November 10, 8353 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 November 17, 8357 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 November 24, 8361 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 1, 8369 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 8, 8375 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 15, 8379 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 23, 8391 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 January 12, 8397 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 2, 8405 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 9, 8409 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 16, 8413 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 23, 8417 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 2, 8425 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 9, 8429 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 16, 8433 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 23, 8437 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 April 13, 8445 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 April 20, 8449 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 April 27, 8453 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 4, 8461 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 11, 8465 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 18, 8469 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 26, 8477 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 5, 8481 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 12, 8485 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 19, 8489 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 26, 8493 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 2, 8497 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 9, 8501 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 16, 8505 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 23, 8509 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 30, 8513 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 December 7, 8517 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 December 14, 8521 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 December 21, 8525 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 January 4, 8529 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 January 11, 8533 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 1, 8537 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 8, 8541 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 15, 8545 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 23, 8549 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 1, 8553 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 8, 8557 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 15, 8561 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 22, 8565 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 29, 8569 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 April 5, 8573 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 April 12, 8577 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 April 26, 8581 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 May 3, 8585 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 May 10, 8591 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 May 17, 8595 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 September 27, 8599 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 4, 8603 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 11, 8607 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 18, 8611 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 25, 8615 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 1, 8619 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 9, 8623 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 15, 8627 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 22, 8631 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 29, 8635 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 December 6, 8639 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 December 13, 8643 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 December 20, 8651 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 January 5, 8655 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 January 10, 8659 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 January 31, 8665 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 7, 8669 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 15, 8673 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 21, 8677 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 28, 8681 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 7, 8687 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 14, 8691 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 23, 8695 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 28, 8699 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 April 11, 8703 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 April 18, 8707 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 April 25, 8711 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 May 2, 8717 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 May 9, 8721 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 May 16, 8727 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 September 28, 8731 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 3, 8735 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 10, 8739 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 17, 8743 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 24, 8747 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 31, 8751 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 8, 8755 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 14, 8759 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 21, 8763 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 28, 8767 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 December 6, 8773 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 December 12, 8777 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 December 19, 8785 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 January 4, 8789 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 January 9, 8793 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 January 30, 8799 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 6, 8805 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 14, 8811 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 20, 8815 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 27, 8819 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 5, 8825 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 12, 8829 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 19, 8833 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 26, 8837 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 2, 8841 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 9, 8849 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 16, 8853 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 30, 8859 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 May 8, 8863 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 May 14, 8867 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 May 21, 8871 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 2, 8875 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 8, 8879 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 16, 8883 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 22, 8887 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 29, 8891 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 6, 8895 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 12, 8899 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 19, 8903 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 26, 8907 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 December 3, 8913 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 December 10, 8917 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 December 17, 8923 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 January 7, 8927 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 January 14, 8931 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 4, 8935 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 11, 8939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 18, 8943 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 26, 8947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 4, 8951 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 11, 8955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 18, 8961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 25, 8965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 1, 8969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 8, 8973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 22, 8977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 29, 8983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 May 6, 8987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 May 13, 8993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Vol. 3, No. 1-29 (duplicates), 1915-1916; 12471 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Vol. 5, No. 1-28 (duplicates), 1917-1918; 12472 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 September 24, 12473 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 September 30, 12474 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 7, 12475 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 15, 12476 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 21, 12477 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 28, 12478 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 5, 12479 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 11, 12480 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 18, 12481 (Box 3, Folder 3)